System Dynamic Society; Records ua435
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Membership Lists, 1984-2002; 0.5 cubic ft.
  This series is made up of the membership lists maintained by the System Dynamic Society. It contains membership lists for every year between 1984 and 2002, excluding 1994.
  Files in this series are arranged chronologically.
  - Membership List, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Membership List, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Membership Directory, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Membership Directory, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Membership List, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Membership Directory, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Membership Directory, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Membership Directory, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Membership Directory, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Membership Directory, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Membership Directory, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Membership Directory, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Membership Directory, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Membership Directory, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Membership Directory, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Membership Directory, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Membership Directory, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Marketing Materials, 1983-2017; 0.33 cubic ft.
  This series is made up of marketing materials created for and distributed by the society. This includes promotional mailers, conference brochures and schedules, and commemorative pens.
  - Non-Conference Marketing Materials, 1983-2017 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Conference Marketing Materials, 2011-2018 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Conference Marketing Materials, 2001-2010 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Conference Commemorative Pens, 2000-2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Conference Market Materials, 1994-2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Conference Marketing Materials, 1983-1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- President's Newsletters, 1988-2016; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Files in this series have been arranged chronologically.
  This series is made up of copies of the Society's newsletter, called the President's Newsletter. Over its history, the newsletter was generally published either annually or biannually depending on society activities. It covers past and upcoming conferences, publications by members and society sponsorship information.
  - President's Newsletters, 1988-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - President's Newsletters, 2000-2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - President's Newsletters, 2006-2018 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Award Recipients, 1997-2019
- Brochures, 2001-2009
  - 2001 System Dynamic Society Brochure, 2001 October 16
  - 2001 Beer Game Brochure, 2001 May 8
  - 2001 Membership Brochure, 2001 May 8
  - 2001 Publications Brochure, 2001 May 8
  - 2002 System Dynamic Society Brochure, 2002 December 16
  - 2002 Beer Game Brochure, 2002 April 18
  - 2002 Membership Brochure, 2002 March 20
  - 2002 Publications Brochure, 2002 April 18
  - 2003 System Dynamic Society Brochure, 2003 February 5
  - 2003 Beer Game Brochure, 2003 February 13
  - 2003 Membership Brochure, 2003 February 13
  - 2003 Publications Brochure, 2003 July 24
  - 2004 Publications Brochure, 2004 February 11
  - 2005 System Dynamic Society Brochure, 2005 February 16
    General
    Original print PDF also available
  - 2005 Beer Game Brochure, 2005 January 28
  - 2005 Membership Brochure, 2005 January 28
  - 2005 Publications Brochure, 2005 January 28
  - 2006 System Dynamic Society Brochure (Never Printed), 2006 May 31
  - 2006 Beer Game Brochure (Never Printed), 2006 January 19
  - 2006 Membership Brochure (Never Printed), 2006 January 19
  - 2006 Publications Brochure (Never Printed), 2006 January 19
  - 2007 System Dynamic Society Brochure, 2006 November 21
  - 2007 Beer Game Brochure, 2007 May 25
  - 2007 Membership Brochure, 2006 October 2
  - 2007 Publications Brochure, 2007 May 25
  - 2008 System Dynamic Society Brochure, 2008 January 30
  - 2008 Beer Game Brochure, 2009 January 12
  - 2008 Membership Brochure, 2008 January 30
  - 2008 Publications Brochure, 2008 December 5
  - 2009 System Dynamic Society Brochure, 2009 February 17
  - 2009 Beer Game Brochure, 2009 January 12
  - 2009 Publications Brochure, 2010 January 14
- Photographs, 1980-2003; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Files in this series have been arranged chronologically. Undated materials have been placed at the end of the series.
  This series is made up of the collection's photographs and negatives. They appear to have been taken at various System Dynamics International Conferences. Also included are several photographs of Jay Forrester, a pioneer in the field of system dynamics.
  - Jay Forrester Photograph, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stirling Scotland Conference Photographs, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Geoffrey Coyle Lifetime Achievement Award Photographs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Quebec Conference Photographs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, cira, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jay and Susan Forrester at Ualbany, Circa, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Conference Photographs, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Jay W. Forrster Stock Photo, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Roberta Spencer and Markus at Conference, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Video Materials, 1999-2003; 1.33 cubic ft.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  This collection contains DVD's, VHS tapes and a Betacam tape that require proper media viewers.
  This series consists of the collection's video materials. Includes video recordings of conference proceedings and Jay Forrester's Ph.D Seminar Series. Also includes VHS and DVD copies of the Society's Beer Game.
  - "A Fire Chat with Joy Forrester" Betacam, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Forrester PhD Seminar in System Dynamics Suggested Readings CD- Roms for PC and Mac on 3 CR-ROM Discs, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Forrester PhD Seminar in System Dynamics Suggested Readings CD- Roms in PAL Format (8 copies), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Jay Forrester Seminar Series Literature Collection DVDs [5 discs], 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Jay Forrester Seminar Series Literature Collection DVD Backup [6 discs], 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jay Forrester Seminar Series Literature Collection Backup (1 DVD-R + 4 CD-R), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Betacam Recording of 19th Annual System Dynamics International Conference in Atlanta, Georgia [Tapes 1+2], 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Forrester PhD Seminar in System Dynamics Sessions A-K Master Copies (11 discs), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Forrester PhD. Seminar in System Dynamics Sessions A-K 2nd Master Copy Set (11 discs), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 1 VHS Tapes 1+2: What's System Dynamics?, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 2 VHS Tapes H2: World Dynamics, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 3 VHS Topics 1+2: Corparate Growth, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 4 VHS Tapes 1+2: Nonlinearity, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 5 VHS Tapes 1+2: Theory, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 6 VHS Tapes 1+2: Group Modelling, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 7 VHS Tapes 1+2: Confidence Models, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 8 VHS Tapes 1+2: National Model, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 9 VHS Tapes 1+2: Ethics, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 10 VHS Tapes 1+2: Management Education, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - System Dynamics Seminar Session 11 VHS Tapes 1+2: The Future of System Dynamics, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- External Digital Media, 1991-2015; 1 cubic ft.
  This series contains CDRs, CD-ROMs and DVD's that require a media viewer. This series also contains one (1) Tweety Bird-shaped Flash Drive, which appears to include materials already present elsewhere in the series.
  This series contains born-digital materials managed on external media, such as CDs and DVDs. Contains materials documenting various conferences that the Society has organized throughout the world, as well as backups of the websites maintained for each year's conference. Materials include recordings of speeches, backups of conference websites, conference proceedings, images, file listings, dissertation copies, and conference brochures.
  Materials in this series are arranged chronologically.
  - Audio of Conference Speeches on CD-RW [2 discs], 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Istanbul, Turkey Conference Proceedings CD (2 copies), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Quebec Conference Proceedings CD, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Geoffrey Coyle Lifetime Achievement Award Photographic CD, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Wellington, New Zealand Conference Proceedings CD-Rom, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bergen, Norway Conference Proceedings CD, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Conference Photographs Disc, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Atlanta, GA Conference Proceedings CD, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Atlanta Conference Photographs (ICD), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Atlanta, Georgia Conference Web Files on CD-R, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Society Newsletter Text and Images CD-R, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CD-RW of Conference Webpages, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Conference Proceedings CD-R, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Conference Web Files, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Conference Proceedings CD-R (New York), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Conference Web Files on CD-R, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Conference Photograph CD (New York City), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Conference Photographs on CD-R (New York), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Starting ST/SD in Your K-12 School" Training Materials on 3 mini-CDs, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Conference Photographs on CD-R: Includes 2003 Conference in New York, 2000 Conference in Bergen, 1991 Conference in Thailand and others (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 2000(Bergen, Norway), 2002 (Palermo, Italy) and 2003 (New York City) Conference Photographs removed from I-drive CD-R, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Oxford, UK Conference Proceedings CD-Rom, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Oxford Conference Photograph (3 CD-R discs), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 2004 Conference Web files on CD-R (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Shannon and Aldo's Oxford and London Photographs on CD-R, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Boston, Massachusetts Conference Preoceedings CD-Rom, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Conference Web Files on CD-R, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Boston Conference Photographs on Mini-CD-R, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Nijmegen Conference Proceedings CD-R (2 Copies), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Online Proceedings ISO Image on 3 CD-R disc, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Conference Webpage and Proceedings for Boston and Nijmegen on 2 CD-R discs, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Online Proceedings and Sub. System Web Archives CD-R discs, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "How the Society Come to Be" Photograph CD-R, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Conference Images (4 discs), 2007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Boston Conference Photographs DVD and CD, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Pegasus Communications Speaker Series on CD-R, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Athens Photographs on CD-R [2 discs], 2008 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Conference Proceedings and Webpage Files on CD-R, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Online Proceedings and Web Subsystem Archives (11 CD-R discs), 2008 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Conference Webpage from Sdsweb and PC minutes on CD-R, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Conference Proceedings and Webpage files on CD-R, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Online Proceedings and sub.sys Archives (4 CD-RW discs), 2009 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Online Proceedings and sub.sys Archives (4 CD-R discs), 2010 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Conference Proceedings and Webpage on CD-R, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Conference Webpage CD-R wihout Proceedings and Photos, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Conference Proceedings and Webpage back [2 CD-Rs], 2011 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Online Proceedings and sub.sys Archives [4 CD-R], 2011 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - SBS 2011 15 Minutes DVD-R (3 Copies) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - SDS Raw Mov Data DVD-R, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Jay W. Forrester Speech DVD-R, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Conference Proceedings and Webpage Back up [3 CD-Rs], 2012 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Online Proceedings and Iso Image (4 CD-R discs), 2012 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - University at Albany CPR Site Files on CD-R, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Conference Proceedings and Webiste Backup (2 CD-Rs), 2013 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Collected Papers of Jay W. Forrester CD-R, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Principles of Systems CD-R, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Conference Proceedings and Webpage Backup (2 CD-Rs), 2014 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Jay Forrester "Why Study System Dynamics?" Video on DVD-R and CDRW, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - SDS Conference Material and Roberta Spencer Files on CDR, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Tweety Bird Flash Drive of Conference Photo, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    ua435_VzKECqdrtxBPgbarEU3JkA
    - Dinner with Jay, 2015 July
      10 JPG Images
    - Head Shots - Karim and Khalid, 2014 September
      3 JPG Images
    - Selected Dean's Pictures, 2015 July
      859 JPG Images
    - Summer School, 2015 July
      32 JPG Images
    - Conference Photos for 2015 Cambridge, MA Conference, 2015 July
      898 JPG images
  - SDSWEB Conference Material on CD-R, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Cambridge, Massachusetts Conference Files from Roberta Spencers Shared Drive SDS Website and SDS Shared Drive, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - CD of Jay Forrester 2-Minute Introductory Speech for George, Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Jay Forrester's Horse + Farmhouse Photographs on CD-R, Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Testimonial on Plato Modelling Work on CD-RW, Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Windows Media File of Dennis Mendows, McNeil Lehrer, NH Crossroads and Peter Jennings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - BP Manufactoring Game: Transformation in the North Sea: Creating Operational Excellence at Bp's Phantom Oilfield Project, Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - D-Memos CD-Rs [4 discs], Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Beer Game NTSC Copy, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - The Beer Game CDs (4 Copies), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Two Copies of Beer Game, Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)